<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>skuzzymiglet&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on skuzzymiglet&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 09:39:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Setup</title>
      <link>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/posts/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 08:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/posts/setup/</guid>
      <description>An update on my setup. I haven&amp;rsquo;t shown it since last October and you people seem to like it.
OS: Arch Linux I love how you get to build your system fully. Yet the rolling release model means you can install and forget, with no worries about updates.
WM: bspwm (switched from i3) I love bspwm&amp;rsquo;s binary tree tiling. It&amp;rsquo;s slightly harder to set up the i3, but I recommend it to anyone with a bit of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 tips</title>
      <link>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/posts/advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 09:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/posts/advice/</guid>
      <description>Just 5 general tips for programming (and other things)
Do it now If you want to do something, just do it. Don&amp;rsquo;t get used to a bug or error. Don&amp;rsquo;t adjust to multiple keypresses. Look it up on GitHub, Stackoverflow or just Google it. It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding fixing things
I struggle to adhere to this sometimes. But it&amp;rsquo;s a rule that pays off
Use it If you make somthing, you should find a use for it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 15:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! This is the first blog post here, just to combat that 404 page! I&amp;rsquo;ll try to post every week from now on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 09:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>A list of my todo, in-progress and done projects
Done  asl - a tool to make timelapses of your screen, replaced asl.sh, a 2-line script, but now I don&amp;rsquo;t use it because it&amp;rsquo;s intrinsically too heavy animator, a command-line animation tool I made in Go. It&amp;rsquo;s kind of stupid, as I knew nothing about animation, so the interface is horrible and the code is functionally flawed  In-progress  point - a simple, fast, tool to create HTML presentation you can open anywhere reviz, a revision app that scans your notes, tests you verbally and shows you your results, all server free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 09:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skuzzymiglet.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I do programming as a hobby. I know Python well, learnt Go in October, I know basic JS (and obviously HTML and CSS) and I&amp;rsquo;m learning Vue. I have many projects to do!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>